<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index on Tony Chang</title>
    <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index on Tony Chang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ClosingBracket.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/about/</guid>
      <description>About#Hello! My name is Tony Chang. I am a rising junior studying Computer Science at the University of Texas at Austin. I will be graduating in the Spring 2022 semester.
Outside of school, I enjoy weightlifting, following international politics, learning about history, and playing video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 1</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog1/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# Where did you grow up?#I have grown up most of my life here in Austin, Texas.
What was your favorite extracurricular activity in high school?#My favorite extracurricular activity in high school was Model UN. I very much enjoyed the people component of Model UN &amp;ndash; having the opportunity to interact with others, having fun representing interests that you weren&amp;rsquo;t too particularly invested in, and just having the opportunity to travel with other club members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 10</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog10/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This past week, I attended class and was mostly focused on recruiting efforts and other classes. I did not have much of an opportunity to work as much on Darwin as I hoped to.
What&amp;rsquo;s in your way?
I have an upcoming Algorithms test on Wednesday that I am also needing to prepare for along with even more interviews, HackerRanks, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 2</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog2/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This past week, I attended Prof. Downing&amp;rsquo;s lectures and got started on the first project, Collatz. At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;ve already cloned the GitLab repository, pushed my first commit to confirm the CI pipeline is working (half working because I have yet to fix the tests yet), and made my first few issues on GitLab issues for the workflow items I need to complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 3</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog3/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This week, I worked to first implement the simplest possible working solution of Collatz. After I was able to confirm that was working, I then implemented the multiplicity of optimizations until my code was able to pass all three HackerRank tests. Afterwards, I followed subsequent steps on the workflow such as making my own unit tests to confirm code functionality and my own acceptance tests for merging on the public test repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 4</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog4/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This week, I learned about throwing and catching exceptions in C++, gained more understanding on the Voting project that we have recently been assigned, and string comparison in C++.
What&amp;rsquo;s in your way?
I feel intimidated by the scale of the Voting project. In the last project, we were given the run and test harness and only needed to handle the actual Collatz logic itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 5</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog5/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This week, I learned more about parameter variables, return variables, references, and pointers in class. Additionally, we learned about how the use of the keyword const modifies each of these types of variables in programs. Finally, we began to cover a short bit of arrays on Friday. In regards to the project, I worked to get my input/output code working (which Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 6</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog6/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This past week, I attended class and learned more about arrays, equals() and iterators in class. I also took my Algorithms exam on Wednesday and worked to complete a few more HackerRanks. Additionally, I was able to finish my Voting project on time and implement all the correct optimizations to get full credit and pass all 3 HackerRank tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 7</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog7/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This past week, I attended class and had the opportunity to learn more about the various strengths of iterators, how these types of iterators applied in various scenarios, and different types of recursion such as regular and tail recursion.
What&amp;rsquo;s in your way?
I have become incredibly bogged down by the homeworks and projects of my other classes along with the demands of fall recruiting, and am finding it hard to dedicate the appropriate time to study for the exam and work on the Allocator project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 8</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog8/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This past week got the chance to make significant progress on the Allocator project we have in OOP and have now mostly finished the project. Additionally, I also studied plenty and constructed a page of notes for the OOP exam. Then, I took the two-part exam on Wednesday and Thursday night!
What&amp;rsquo;s in your way?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang - Week 9</title>
      <link>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ClosingBracket.github.io/docs/oop/blog9/</guid>
      <description>CS371p Fall 2020: Tony Chang# What did you do this past week?
This past week, I finished my Allocator project and was able to successfully turn the project in. I finished a take-home exam in my other class, and was able to attend class and learn about Darwin, the new project that we have been most recently assigned. Additionally, I was able to make progress on recruiting and finished a few HackerRanks that I have been pushing off for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>